// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions2 = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "I am in my teens.",
    answer: "be + in age",
    options: [
      "be + in age",
      "be + about age",
      "be + adjective + with + and (age + feature)",
      "be + of build",
      "have or have got features"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "They are about sixty",
    answer: "be + about age",
    options: [
        "be + in age",
        "be + about age",
        "be + adjective + with + and (age + feature)",
        "be + of build",
        "have or have got features"
      ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "I am middle-aged with curly hair and dark eyes.",
    answer: "be + adjective + with + and (age + feature)",
    options: [
        "be + in age",
        "be + about age",
        "be + adjective + with + and (age + feature)",
        "be + of build",
        "have or have got features"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "You are in your early twenties",
    answer: "be + in age",
    options: [
        "be + in age",
        "be + about age",
        "be + adjective + with + and (age + feature)",
        "be + of build",
        "have or have got features"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 5,
    question: "I am of average height.",
    answer: "be + of build",
    options: [
        "be + in age",
        "be + about age",
        "be + adjective + with + and (age + feature)",
        "be + of build",
        "have or have got features"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "I have blue eyes",
    answer: "have or have got features",
    options: [
        "be + in age",
        "be + about age",
        "be + adjective + with + and (age + feature)",
        "be + of build",
        "have or have got features"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "He is in his mid thirties.",
    answer: "be + in age",
    options: [
        "be + in age",
        "be + about age",
        "be + adjective + with + and (age + feature)",
        "be + of build",
        "have or have got features"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "He is of medium build",
    answer: "be + of build",
    options: [
        "be + in age",
        "be + about age",
        "be + adjective + with + and (age + feature)",
        "be + of build",
        "have or have got features"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "I have got dark hair",
    answer: "have or have got features",
    options: [
        "be + in age",
        "be + about age",
        "be + adjective + with + and (age + feature)",
        "be + of build",
        "have or have got features"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "She is in her late forties",
    answer: "be + in age",
    options: [
        "be + in age",
        "be + about age",
        "be + adjective + with + and (age + feature)",
        "be + of build",
        "have or have got features"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 11,
    question: "She is about twenty-five",
    answer: "be + about age",
    options: [
        "be + in age",
        "be + about age",
        "be + adjective + with + and (age + feature)",
        "be + of build",
        "have or have got features"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 12,
    question: "She is elderly with a long face and glasses",
    answer: "be + adjective + with + and (age + feature)",
    options: [
        "be + in age",
        "be + about age",
        "be + adjective + with + and (age + feature)",
        "be + of build",
        "have or have got features"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 13,
    question: "He has a fair complexion and short, curly hair",
    answer: "have or have got features",
    options: [
        "be + in age",
        "be + about age",
        "be + adjective + with + and (age + feature)",
        "be + of build",
        "have or have got features"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 14,
    question: "We are in our fifties",
    answer: "be + in age",
    options: [
        "be + in age",
        "be + about age",
        "be + adjective + with + and (age + feature)",
        "be + of build",
        "have or have got features"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 15,
    question: "They are of medium weight",
    answer: "be + of build",
    options: [
        "be + in age",
        "be + about age",
        "be + adjective + with + and (age + feature)",
        "be + of build",
        "have or have got features"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 16,
    question: "He's got fair hair and a bushy beard",
    answer: "have or have got features",
    options: [
        "be + in age",
        "be + about age",
        "be + adjective + with + and (age + feature)",
        "be + of build",
        "have or have got features"
    ]
  },

// you can uncomment the below codes and make duplicate as more as you want to add question
  // but remember you need to give the numb value serialize like 1,2,3,5,6,7,8,9.....

  //   {
  //   numb: 6,
  //   question: "Your Question is Here",
  //   answer: "Correct answer of the question is here",
  //   options: [
  //     "Option 1",
  //     "option 2",
  //     "option 3",
  //     "option 4"
  //   ]
  // },
];